EGOR NAZAROV

+7(952) 643-4809 \diamond Saint-Petersburg, Russia

nazarov.egor2010@yandex.ru \langle linkedin.com/in/nazzrrg \langle t.me/nazzrrg \langle github.com/nazzrrg

OBJECTIVE

Software Engineer with 3 years of experience in back-end development. Looking for full-time Senior Golang Backend Developer positions.

My superpower is the ability to balance between "tactical" and "strategical" programming, allowing me to deliver new features without getting bogged down by technical debt.

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Science, ITMO University, Saint-Petersburg, Russia Bachelor of Programming and Internet Technology, ITMO University, Saint-Petersburg, Russia

SKILLS

Engineering Skills Golang, gRPC/REST/Kafka + protobuf, PostgreSQL/MongoDB/Redis, JavaScript

System Design Microservices, DDD, CQRS and Event Sourcing, GoF design patterns

Tools Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift, Jenkins, Prometheus, Grafana, ELK-stack, Postman

Soft Skills TDD, BDD, Agile(SCRUM), balancing New Features and Technical Debt

Language Skills Russian - native, English - proficient

EXPERIENCE

Sber — Senior Software Engineer

Saint-Petersburg, Russia Jan 2024 - Present

- Led a major refactor and error handling optimisation, which postponed a complete rewrite of the service by 2+ years.
- Achieved 20% CPU load reduction for one of the microservices through finding an optimal logging solution.
- Developed a microservice based contact centre solution for the largest contact centre in Europe (300,000+calls/day) using Golang, PostgreSQL, Kafka, REST, gRPC, OpenShift, ELK.

Sellematics — Software Engineer

Dubai, UAE Aug 2023 - Jan 2024

- Led the development of a web-fingerprint farming service which led to **75% reduction in fingerprint-related errors**.
- Developed a scraper and parser components for Online Marketplace Analytics Platform using Golang, Redis, MongoDB, Sentry, Prometheus, Grafana and Wireshark.

Initi — Software Engineer

Moscow, Russia Mar 2022 - Jul 2023

- Pioneered automated testing in the project, which led to 50X reduction of manual testing time for the component and 10% improvement in delivery speed for the whole project.
- Developed a Network and Application Monitoring Solution using a proprietary language, **ClickHouse and Python**.

Diasoft — Junior Software Engineer

Saint-Petersburg, Russia Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

• Developed Apache modules that prepared data for a resource management system using C++ and OracleDB.

LEADERSHIP

• Sep 2021 - May 2022 - freshman mentor. Helped with the adaptation of new students in academic environment. Provided guidance and assistance as well as organised activities aimed at ice-breaking and team-building.